dining-out.co.za 2019-09-25

# Privacy Policy

Our Commitment to Privacy

Dining-OUT values its customers and respects their privacy. We collect customer information in an effort to improve your online experience and to communicate with you about our products, services, contests, and promotions. Dining-OUT recognizes that it must maintain and use customer information responsibly. We do not sell or rent the information you provide to us online to third parties. However, we do share your information with third parties under certain circumstances. This policy describes the personal information we collect about you, why we collect it, how we use it and when we share it with third parties. Our policy also describes the choices you can make about how we collect and use your information. If you have any questions about our privacy policy, click here to contact Dining-OUT customer service via email or call us on 27-21-7621543. If our information practices change in the future, we will let you know by posting the policy changes on our Web site or by communicating directly with you. We will notify you of any such change before we use your information in a manner not previously disclosed in our privacy policy. You will have the opportunity at that time to opt out of any new use of your information. 

Frequently Asked Questions: 

What kind of information does Dining-OUT collect?  
We collect information (such as your name, email address, mailing address, and phone numbers) that you provide when you save your information with us or participate in a contest, promotion or survey. We also maintain a record of your interests such as geographic areas and food types. We may acquire customer names, email addresses and mailing addresses for select mailings from third parties. 

How does Dining-OUT use my information? 

When you make an online reservation via Dining-OUT, we use your information to process your booking. We will also send you emails to confirm your booking, and we may need to contact you via phone or email if we have other questions regarding your booking. When you register yourself or your friends with our Guest Book, we use your information to send you and your friends news and events relating to the restaurants in the areas you select. To serve you better, we may combine information you give us online as well as information about your interests . In addition, we may combine information you provide with demographic information that is publicly available. We use this combined information to enhance and personalize your online experience with us, and to communicate with you by email about our products, services, contests, and promotions that may be of interest to you. If you do not want us to use your information as described above, please contact Dining-OUT customer service via email or call us on 27-21-7621543. 

Does Dining-OUT share my information with third parties? 

We may contract with third parties to assist us in maintaining and managing our customer information to fulfil promotions and to communicate with our customers. We do not authorize any of those third parties to make any other use of your information. In addition, when we team up with another company to offer or provide products, services, contests or promotions, we and the other company may cross-reference our customer databases to identify common customers. We and the other company may use that existing information to identify future promotional opportunities and to fulfil promotional or contractual obligations. When we offer contests and promotions, or join with other companies to do so, customers who choose to participate in those contests and promotions may be asked to provide personal information to participate. This information may then be used by us and any company offering the contest or promotion to notify winners or to fulfil promotional obligations. If prior to participating in a contest or promotion, you opted not to receive information from us, you may still receive information from or about Dining-OUT in connection with the contest or promotion if you choose to participate in it. You may opt not to participate in these contests or promotions if you do not want to receive information about Dining-OUT or share your information with us and the other companies sponsoring those contests or promotions. We also may share aggregate, non-personally identifiable information about you (such as age, gender, and interests) with our business partners to fulfil our contractual obligations. Except as described above, we do not share, rent or sell any information we collect online to any unaffiliated third party. 

How do I remove my information from email, phone, and postal mailing lists? 

We want to communicate with you only if you want to hear from us. If you prefer not to receive information from us, either through email or by phone, please let us know by sending us an email. Please note that such requests may take up to six to eight weeks to become effective. In addition, if you ask us to remove your name and address from our email mailing lists, we will maintain your name in a "do not mail" file to ensure that we can honour your request. Please also note that when you make an online reservation , we will send you emails to confirm your booking and may also need to contact you via phone or email if we have other questions regarding your booking. 

What are cookies? How does Dining-OUT use cookies on its site? 

A cookie is a small data file that Web sites often store on your computer's hard drive when you visit their sites. A cookie may contain information (such as a unique user ID), that is used to track the pages of the sites you've visited. We use cookies but do not store personally identifiable information in your cookie. We use cookies in order to improve your online experience. If you have saved your information with us, your cookie allows us to recognize you when you return to our site in order to monitor and maintain information about your use of our site. If you have not saved your information with us, we may monitor and maintain information about your use of our Web site in a manner that does not identify you. In either case, this information helps us serve you better by improving our site design, as well as our products, services, contests, and promotions. We also use cookies to track and maintain the identity of the Web site you visited immediately prior to ours to further improve our site design and to fulfil contracts with our business partners. We do not otherwise track any information about your use of other Web sites. You can refuse cookies by turning them off in your browser.
